Guide to the James L. Vizzard Papers, 1942-1983
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VI: SUBJECT FILES, 1953-1977
  - Subseries D. Migrants, 1953-1967
    - Newsclippings, 1961-1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Rio Grande City, Texas 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Subseries E. Public Law 78
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Mar.-May, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, June-July, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Oct., 1963-Feb., 1965 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Press coverage, 1957-1967 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Statements, 1958-1964 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F. Westlands Water District/160-Acre Limitation, 1956-1977
    - Congressional Record, 1947-1976 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, out-going, 1956-1967 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, in-coming, 1957-1962 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, in-coming, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, in-coming, 1965-1966 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Newsclippings, 1947-1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany, 1962-1966 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany (1), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany (2), 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Statements, reports and miscellany, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Dr. Paul S., 1956-1961 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Dr. Paul S., 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, Dr. Paul S, 1965-1967 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- SERIES VII: ORAL HISTORY, 1980
  - Oral history tape and partial transcript; Vizzard interviewed by Anne Loftis, Nov. 22, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- SERIES VIII: PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Group photograph, signed by Norris E. Dodd and Bernard W. Miller, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Group photographs (including Vizzard), n.d. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Photographs from migrant case histories (Box 31, Folder 1), ca. 1963 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Portrait photographs of Vizzard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Teamster strike breakers, ca. 1973 (Box 33, Folder 12)